Sidebery provides the list of tabs structured in a tree, bookmarks and history within the customizable panels. It aims to be fast and configurable. Some of the key features:

<strong>- Tabs</strong>
- Simple flat list or tree with the option to set tree limit.
- Group tabs (aka folders) with a custom name helps organize open pages.
- Tabs colorization: Automatic per-domain/URL or manual.
- Automatic unloading of tabs in a folded branch / inactive panel.
- Customizable tab title.
- ...

<strong>- Bookmarks</strong>
- Tree or chronological view.
- Sort by name, URL or creation time
- Basic operations: open in... / create / edit / delete.
- Ability to highlight open bookmarks and activate the corresponding tab instead of opening a new one when clicked.
- Automatically delete a bookmark on opening from "Other Bookmarks" folder or configured bookmarks panel.
- ...

<strong>- Tabs / Bookmarks panels</strong>
- Organize your browsing with panels of tabs/bookmarks.
- Convert open tabs in the panel to bookmarks and vice versa.
- Automatically move tabs by URL to configured panel.
- ...

<strong>- Containers</strong>
- Bind container to the tabs panel.
- Automatically reopen tab in the target container by URL.
- Setup proxy config and UserAgent header for tabs in a container.
- ...

<strong>- Customizable context menu</strong>
Sidebery allows you to change the context menu for tabs and bookmarks. You can enable/disable/move options, create sub-menus/separators.

<strong>- Customizable mouse/keyboard controls</strong>
- Option to switch tabs with mouse-wheel.
- Configurable drag and drop behavior.
- A growing list of available actions for mouse/keyboard bindings.

<strong>- Customizable styles</strong>
Sidebery provides full control of styles for sidebar and group page via variables and custom CSS.

<strong>- Snapshots</strong>
You can setup auto snapshots that will keep info about open windows and tabs.


<strong>Privacy policy</strong>
<ul>
Sidebery keeps all data that needed to correct work on the user's machine and doesn't send any kind of data to the outside.
</ul>


<strong>Source code</strong>
<ul>
Source code can be found here: <a href="https://github.com/mbnuqw/sidebery">https://github.com/mbnuqw/sidebery</a>
</ul>


<strong>Permissions</strong>
<ul>
- Read and modify bookmarks - needed for bookmarking the tabs and bookmarks panel functionality.
- Access recently closed tabs - needed for the "Undo close tab" function.
- Access browser tabs - needed to get info and control tabs.
</ul>


<strong>Optional permissions</strong>
<ul>
- Websites Data - Required for next features:
<ul>
- Context menu option for cleaning cookies
- Proxy and url rules of containers
- Page-screenshots for the group page and windows selection panel
- Changing the User-Agent per container
</ul>
- Hiding tabs - Required for next features:
<ul>
- Hiding tabs on inactive panels
- Hiding folded tabs
</ul>
- Clipboard write - Context menu option for copying urls of tabs and bookmarks
- Web requests blocking - Changing the User-Agent per container
- Control browser proxy settings - needed for proxy configuration per container and it can be used only with granted optional permission "Websites Data".
</ul>
Note: You can deny these permissions at any time on the settings page.

<strong>Notes</strong>
<ul>
- Firefox doesn't allow addons to hide the native (horizontal) tab bar. To achieve that, you can use <a href="https://github.com/mbnuqw/sidebery/wiki/Firefox-Styles-Snippets-(via-userChrome.css)">userChrome.css hacks</a>.
</ul>

<strong>Donate to support the development of this project</strong>
<ul>
- Bitcoin (BTC): bc1q2drx3x5pfl0c68urwztvjrwgksg9u3l7mn4g4m
- Ethereum (ETH), USDT (ERC20), USDC (ERC20): 0x11667D20AB328194AEEc68F9385CCcf713607929
- USDT (TRC20), USDC (TRC20): TJEdp1TnsN7Jfhfi9Db8yXKDK8NEUovCZb
</ul>

<strong><a href="https://github.com/mbnuqw/sidebery#readme">More info you can find here</a></strong>
